#### Contact

mccullumlegal@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/marilyn-mccullum-rn-bsn-legal-nurse-consultant-67a09493 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Emergency Medicine
Legal Nurse Consulting
Legal Document Preparation

### Languages

English (Native or Bilingual) Spanish (Native or Bilingual)

### Certifications

**NIHSS** 

PALS

**TNCC** 

BLS

**ACLS** 

# Marilyn McCullum RN, BSN, Legal Nurse Consultant

Bilingual Emergency Medicine Legal Nurse Consultant and Expert Witness

San Francisco Bay Area

## Summary

Marilyn is a registered nurse who has been working in emergency rooms and trauma centers across the United States for 15 years, and is now using that experience to help people as a legal nurse consultant. Marilyn has an extensive history of medical terminology, medical charting, and the ability to assess for effective medical care while maintaining nationwide quality standards. Her skills in medicine and nursing are exhaustive, and she is confident her additional strengths will readily translate to your firm.

Marilyn is available for medical chart reviews, chronologies, as an expert witness, and DME/IME observation.

## Experience

Kaiser Permanente Emergency Room Registered Nurse January 2018 - Present (2 years 7 months) Santa Rosa, CA

Self-Employed Contractor Registered Nurse Travel RN 2013 - Present (7 years)

St. Joseph Health Emergency Room Nurse November 2015 - January 2018 (2 years 3 months) Santa Rosa, CA

St. Joseph Medical Center Travel Nurse May 2015 - October 2015 (6 months) Hazel Hawkins Memorial Hospital Travel Nurse February 2015 - March 2015 (2 months) Hollister, CA

Sunrise Medical Center
Travel Nurse
October 2014 - November 2014 (2 months)
Las Vegas, Nevada Area

Community Regional Medical Centers Travel Nurse April 2014 - September 2014 (6 months) Fresno, California Area

Southwestern Vermont Medical Center Travel Nurse January 2014 - April 2014 (4 months) Woodford, Vermont

Wilson Medical Center
Travel Nurse
July 2013 - December 2013 (6 months)
Wilson, North Carolina

St Vincent's Health Travel Nurse May 2013 - May 2013 (1 month) Little Rock, Arkansas Area

University of Louisville Hospital Emergency Room Nurse July 2012 - April 2013 (10 months) Louisville, Kentucky Area

Floyd Memorial Hospital and Health Services Emergency Room Nurse June 2011 - July 2012 (1 year 2 months) New Albany, IN Norton Healthcare Emergency Room Technician September 2005 - May 2011 (5 years 9 months)

Louisville, Kentucky Area

# Education

Indiana University-Southeast
Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2012)

Kentucky State University
Associate's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse